Hail Siya Ram.  Friends, in this video we are going to
talk
about the quarter 4 results of ICI LBD company.  So, just a
while ago the company has
presented its quarter 4 results.  Let us
see how the quarterly results of the company were.
Before that, if
we look, along with its results, the company has
also issued its final dividend here.  The
company has issued dividend here on the share at ₹7.
After this, if we
talk about data, then whatever value is
given here is given in lakhs.  I will
convert it into crores and share it with you.
So let us see what the results of the company are.  First of all,
if we
talk about the total income of the company.  So,
if we look at the March quarter of last year, the
company's income was around Rs
5165 crore.
If we look at the last quarter, it was around Rs 582 crore.
If we look at this quarter, there is a
slight decline in the company's income.  The
company's income this time has been Rs
5851 crore.   There is an
annual jump visible in it.  But
if we compare it quarterly, there is a
slight decline in it.  So
after the income, let us look at the expenses of the company.  From this
we will basically get an idea whether the company has been profitable this year
or is making a loss.
So if we look at the same quarter last year, the
company's expenses were Rs 463 crore.
Which had increased to Rs 55197 crore in the last quarter.
And if we look at this year also, the
company's expenses seem to be increasing both annually and quarterly.
This time the company's expenses were around Rs 5435 crore.
So if we look at the company's expenses, there is a
jump visible both annually and quarterly.  So basically, this
is a clear indication that the profitability of the company this time may be
seen falling both quarterly and annually.
After that, if we
check the profit after tax of the company, then
last year the profit made by the company was Rs
519 crore in the same quarter.
In the last quarter, the company had made a profit
of Rs 724 crore and
if we look at this quarter, the company has made a
profit of about Rs 509 crore.  So,
if we compare the profitability of the company quarterly and
annually, it seems to be falling.
So if we compare the company's results, the
company's profit has fallen quarterly and annually.
So there is a clear indication
that the company's results were
not that special.  We can say that the company has
presented very poor numbers here.
After this we basically check the EPS of the company.
So last year, if we
look at the same quarter, the EPS of the company was
around 10.5, which
increased to around 15 in the last quarter.
So this year also, if we
look at the EPS of the company, it
seems to be falling on quarterly and annual basis.
Because this time, if we look at the company's
sales, they have increased annually but there is a
decline in them quarterly.
Along with that, if we look at the expenses of the company, they seem to be
increasing both annually and quarterly.  Obviously, if the
company's expenses increase, the company's
profit will be seen falling.  The same thing has
happened with this company also.  It will be interesting to see
how the market reacts to this when it opens tomorrow.  That's all
in this video.  If you
like the video then like the video
and don't forget to subscribe to the channel.